let let me talk about the
compounded because here in Europe we
only have the big Brands we have monjaro
now we have OIC but here there's no
compounding glp ones so that's an
interesting concept like this past
summer I was in in um in London and I
had a really good podcast and we were
discussing that there's no compounds in
Europe but the price of it is
€150 whereas the price of out of pocket
in the US is $1,000 to $1,500 the exact
same brand exact same company why is it
so expensive in the US and in the US
it's not even um available right now the
makers of Mount jao and ZB bound say
that they have enough that they could
really Supply the whole Market but I
don't believe it there are so many
patients on compound that if they were
to stop the the the flow of compounds
there's no way Eli L and Nova NES would
be able to keep up with the demand so
right now what's happening in the US is
that there's a lot of reshuffling and
some of the pharmacies especially the
503b pharmacies that are FDA inspected
are doing the right thing are
compounding it the right way so until I
can see that the prices go down and that
people have can afford it and they can
find it there is going to have to be a
possibility of using compound and right
now the big boys the big guys have
entered this Market you know hims the
company hims and hers they started
ordering compounded glp1 medication and
they have hund millions of patients so
the Gen is not going to go back in the
bottle Eli Eli Eli and noo NIS I'm
hoping that they can really rimp up
production and make it glp1 cheaper so
that everybody can get the brand name
until that happens those medications are
too important to restrict them because
some cannot afford them
[Music]